DAVID BALDUS PAPERS (APAP329) 1965-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Military Study, 1995-2011; 16; 21.3
  - Subject FilesMIL, 1995-2011; 16.1; 15.3
    - Correspondence - Dwight Sullivan, Dick Newell Military Job, 2005 November 22-23 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - Cathi Grosso, Scheduling, 2005 December 6 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - Dick Newell Military Jobs, Race of Hassan Akbar Victim, 2005 December 6-7 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Michael Shroder [not eligible?], 2005 December 12; 2006 March 8; 2007 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - Dick Newell, Military Job, 2005 December 18 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - Student Researchers, 2005 December 28; 2006 January 3 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - DC Interns, Payroll [Restricted], 2005 December-2006 January (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Richard Berk, General Deterrene, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Case lists, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Corrections to Ronald Gray Narrative Summary, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Document 3 - Disposition of U.S. Military Death - Eligible Cases: 1984 to Present, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Document 4 - Pilot Study Data Collection Instrument (D.C.I.), ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Document 5 - Pilot Study Preliminary Findings, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Document 6 - Student Interns case gathering checklist, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Document 7 - Check - off sheet for copied documents, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Document 8 - Data Collection Instrument (D.C.I.), ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Document 9 - Mitigation Code Appendix, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Document 10 - Militart Rank and Grade, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Document 11 - U.S. Military Medals, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Document 12 - Dwight H. Sullivan, "Two Decades of Military Capital Litigation,", ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Document 13 - David A. Schlueter, "Military Criminal Justice: Practice and Procedure, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Document 14 - Select Bibliography, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Document 15 - Alllen L. Justice, Sr. Case, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Document unnumbered - United States V. Gibbs, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Document unnumbered, United States V. Kreutzer, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Document unnumbered, United States V. Loving, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Notes - Military Master List, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Working Papers - Mitigating Circumstances, Data Collection Instrument (DCI), 2005 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence - Major Bill Ruhling on David Burtlett and Jerry Brown, 2006 January 3 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Purgell PHAT Procedure, 2006 January 4 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - U.S. Army Corrections System: Procedures for Military Executions, 2006 January 17 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence - Dwight Loving and Ronald Gray, 2006 January 27 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Contract Information - John Payton, Jamie Gorelick, Kevin J. Berry, Walter T. Cox the 3rd, 2006 February 6; 2006 July 19 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence - Cathi Grosso, Dwight Sullivan, 2006 February 6; 2006 October 9; 2006 November 1 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Unadjusted Sisparities in Death Sentence Rates Among all Death Eligible Cases, 2006 February 7; 2006 March 10 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence - Two Vic Procedural Cleaning, 2006 February 9; 2006 March 28 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - List of Recorded Variables, in binder, 2006 February 17; 2006 March 9 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - All Grequency Distributions for Nonmissing Variables, 2006 February 18 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Data Reports - All Frequencey Distributions for Nonmissing Variables, 2006 February 18 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Frequencey Distribution - DCI, recodes, 2006 February 18 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - History of Records, 2006 February 19; 2006 March 14 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence - Cathi Grosso, Wilmer/Cutting, 2006 February 20 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence - Human Rights Watch, 2006 February 21 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence - Human Rights Watch, 2006 February 21 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Massachusettes Death Penalty Statute, 2006 February 24 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Records and Variables, Cleaning, 2006 February 24; 2006 February 28 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence - Military Officers Association of America (MOAA), National Institute of Military Justice (NSMJ) Jag Officer Recruitment Samples, 2006 February 27; 2006 March 6-10 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Sources of Raters, 2006 February 27-March 6 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Dwight Sullivan Capital Trial, 2006 February 27-March 6; 2006 April 17-19 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Data Reports - Death Cases, 2006 February 28 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Correspondence - Institutional Review Board, Cathi Grosso notes on DCI, Video Conference, 2006 February; 2006 October; 2006 November; 2007 February (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Correspondence - Dwight Sullivan, National Institute for Military Justice, 2006 March 1 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Pilot Database, Alphabetical by last name, in binder, 2006 March 1 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Correspondence - Loving and Gray Defense Team, 2006 March 2 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence - George Woodworth Analysis, Power, 2006 March 3 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Stephanie Traum [not death eligible?], 2006 March 5; 2007 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Macro #1-11, 2006 March 7 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - New Cases, 2006 March 7 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Data Reports - R-squared, Cleaning, define standard Marcos, Offender Culpability, Variable Case, Minority accused, 2006 March 9; 2006 March 12; 2006 March 15 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Detailed Narrative Summaries for Death-Eligible Prosecutions, 2006 March 9 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Key Variables, 2006 March 9; 2006 March 25-27; 2006 May 10; 2006 June 27; 2006 July 7 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - SAS Procedures, 2006 March 9-12 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Cleaning Jobs to Deck, 2006 March 11 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Data Reports - Small Logit Models, 2006 March 12 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Variable Cleanng - Death Penalty Recodes, 2006 March 12-19 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Correspondence - Hassan Akbar, 2006 March 14 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Clean Outcomes, 2006 March 13 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Data Reports - Logistic Regression, 2006 March 15 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Correspondence - George Woodwoth on PHATS, 2006 March 17-18 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Binder - SAS Statistical Procedures in David Baldus Computer, 2006 March 18 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Methodology - Stat Issues, 2006 March 19 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Correspondence - Pardon Counsel, 2006 March 20 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Data Reports - Two Vic Adjusted, 2006 March 20 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Data - Two Victim Analysis, Unadjusted, 2006 March 20 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Data Reports - Two Victim Lists, 2006 March 20 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Handwritten Notes - George Woodworth Issues, 2006 March 20 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Table 1 (Branch), 2006 March 20 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Correspondence - Dwight Sullican Comments, 2006 March 21; 2006 July 18; 2006 July 21; 2006 August 3 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Data Reports - Two victim, early stages, 2006 March 22 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Data Reports - White Victim by Victim Cases, 2006 March 22 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Co-prepetrators in Military Cases, 2006 March 24 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Co-Perpetrators Screen, to Cathi, 2006 March 25 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Two Victim Verifications, 2006 March 25-28 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Variable Cleaning - Death - Elgible Co - prep citations, 2006 March 25-2006 April 14 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Data Reports - scale created, 2006 March 26 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Handwritten Notes Screening, Death 1, 2006 March 26 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Variable Cleaning - Age, 2006 March 26 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Data Reports - Crosstabs, Death by Age, 2006 March 28 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Screening Results for Death 1 Variable, 2006 March 28 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - George Woodworth, 5 Models, Core Model, 2006 March 29 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Data Reports - Black Defendant, White Victim and Death Sentence before CA review, Tables and Figures, FOIL Abbreviations, 2006 March 29; 2006 April 1; 2006 April 6 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Methodology - Fit of the model, models specification, 2006 March 29; 2006 April 2; 2006 April 19 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Variable Cleaning, 2006 March 29 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Handwritten Notes - George Woodworth, Core Model, 2006 March 30 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - Table on Charcteristics, 2006 March 31 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Data Reports - Branch Offices, 2006 March 31 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Inventory of Medals and Ribbons, 2006 March 31 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Military Background Research Statistics, 2006 March 31-April 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Table 2 (Occupation), 2006 March 31 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Database Tasks - Rob Ramsey Model, 2006 March (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Figures for Military Pilot Study [with variable cleaning], ca. 2006 March-April (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Handwritten Notes - Descriptive Statistics, ca. 2006 March (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Data Reports - Table 1A, Figure 9, proof list, 2006 April 1; 2006 July 6-8 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Variable Cleaning, 2006 April 1-2 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Data Reports - Crosstabs by Branch, 2006 April 2 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Data Reports - Culpability Scale, B_W3_Scale_Sand 6, 2006 April 2-9 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Methodology - Race Effects with Purged Index, 2006 April 2 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Methodology - Wave 3 Purges, 2006 April 2 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Table 3 (Pay Grade), 2006 April 2 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Table 4 (Age), 2006 April 2 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Table 5 (Race), 2006 April 2 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Table 6 (Main Effect Regression), 2006 April 2; 2006 April 5; 2006 April 9 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Data Reports - 5 Level Culpability Scale, not adjusted, 2006 April 3 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Student interns - Ranking Aggravating Factors, 2006 April 3-4 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Table 2 (Ranking of Two Victim Cases with Rationale, 2006 April 4; 2006 July 13 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Student Cleaning, Two Victum Rating #1, 2006 April 4 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Comprative Models - Aggravating Factors, George Woodworth, 2006 April 5 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Tables and Figures, with Handwritten notes, 2006 April 5-10; 2006 May 18-30 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Variable Cleaning - High Danger, 2006 April 5 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Variable Cleaning - Sandra Goveia procedure Alan Clark, 2006 April 6 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Handwritten Notes George Woodworth, Coefficients Explain, ca. 2006 April 7 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Table 9 - Logistic Models with Black Defendant, White Victim Interaction terms, 2006 April 7-12 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Purge Procedure - PHATS with Race, 2006 April 8 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Table 7 (Interaction Regression), 2006 April 9; 2006 May 7 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Student Coding Validations - Sandra Goveria, procedures for Kirklan Curry, 2006 April 9 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, Handwritten Notes - Summary of Funding and Methological, 2006 April 10; 2006 April 29; 2006 May 6 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Insert - Sample Size, 2006 April 10; 2006 August 6 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Sample Size Problem, 2006 April 10 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Draft - "Equal Justice and The Death Penalty, " Tables and Figures Handout, 2006 April 12 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Draft - "Equal Justice and the Death Penalty," Tables and Figures Handout, 2006 April 12 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Ill Handout - "Equal Justice and the Death Penalty: The Experience of the United States Armed Forces (1984 - 2005) - Tables and Figures Handout, 2006 April 12 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Methodology - George Woodworth Interaction, 2006 April 12; 2006 April 19 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Presentation - University of Illinois, 2006 April 12; 2006 April 17 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Workshop - "Equal Justice and the Death Penalty: The Experience of the United States Armed Forces (1984 - 2005) - Tables and Figures Handout, 2006 April 12 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Variable Cleaning, 2006 April 17 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Variable Cleaning, 2006 April 17 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Figure 10b (5 level), 2006 April 19; 2006 April 24 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Variable Cleaning - Two Victim threat measure, 2006 April 19 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - History of the Military Death Penalty Background Research, 2006 April 24; 2006 May 21-26 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Military Cases - United States V. Curtis and United States V. Loving, Case Summaries with handwritten notes, 2006 April 24 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Notes, Data Reports, Recodes, Cathi Grosso Correspondence, Barnett's Measure, 2006 April 25-26; 2006 May 10; 2006 May 20 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Figures 10 C (4 - Level), 2006 April 25 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Correspondence, Data Reports - Capital Sentencing Hearing Death Penalty (CSHDTH) Models, 2006 April 26; 2006 June 10 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - History of the Military Death Penalty, 2006 April 30 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Presentation - "Equal Justice and The Death Penalty" The Experience of the Armed Forces of the United States (1984 - 2005), Race and the Death Penalty Conference, Harvard Law School, 2006 April 30; 2006 May 6 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Narrative Summaries, ca. 2006 April (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Dependent Children (no table), ca. 2006 April (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Table 4 (Gender), ca. 2006 April (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Table 6 (Ethnicity), ca. 2006 April (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Table 7 (Marital Status), ca. 2006 April (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Student Coding Validations - Procedural Cleanings, ca. 2006 April (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Correspondence - Cathi Grosso on Dwight Loving and Ronald Gray, 2006 May 1 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - History of the Military Death Penalty, 2006 May 1 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - History of the Military Death Penalty, 2006 May 1-2 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Stack Jury System and Military Death Penalty Legislations, 2006 May 2-3; 2006 May 16 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Correspondence - CAAF Decisions on Propartionality Review, 2006 May 3 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Correspondence - Cathi Grosso, Proportionality Review in Military, 2006 May 3 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Database Notes - Harvard Conference, 2006 May 5-6 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Presentation - "Equal Justice and the Death Penalty: The Experience of the United States Armed Forces (1984 - 2005), Harvard Law School Institute for Race and Justice, Race and the Death Penalty, 2006 May 5-6 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Data Reports - CA seek with scales, 2006 May 7 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Death Penalty Information Center Website, 2006 May 8; 2006 May 18-30 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Department of Defense Authorization Act 1986 - Title I: Procurement - Part A: Funding, 2006 May 8 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - History of the Military Death Penalty - Articles to Read, 2006 May 8 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Scanned Files Case Lists and Inventories, 2006 May 15-2007 September 28 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Social Scrence Research Newwork (SSRN) Submission and Conference Submission, 2006 May 16; 2006 June 30; 2006 July 5-6 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Data Reports - Death Sentence Year, FREQ Procedure, 2006 May 16 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - JEHT Foundation Grant - Approval of Suplemental Request, 2006 May 16; 2006 June 5 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - JEHT Foundation Grant - Supplemental Request Application, 2006 May 16 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Data Reports - Child Victim - Logistic Procedure, 2006 May 18 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Data Reports - Family Variables, 2006 May 18 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Data Reports - n=16, Death 1, Black Defendant, 2 Scales, 2006 May 18 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Data Reports - n=16, Death 1, Black defendant, White Victim, 2 Scales, 2006 May 18 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Data Reports - Scale Counters, 2006 May 18 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Data Reports - Branch Effects, 2006 May 19 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Data Reports - Negotiated Plea, 2006 May 19 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Data Reports - Results by Branch of Service, 2006 May 19 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Cathi Grosso - Code for Factos and Factor Scales, 2006 May 19 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - JEHT Foundation Grant - Proposal Routing Form and Grant Account, 2006 May 19; Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - George Woodworth Records, 2006 May 19-22 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Data Reports - Death Variables, 2006 May 20-28 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Data Reports - n=16, Death 1, 3 Factos, Black Defendany, 2006 May 20 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Data Reports - n=16, Death 1, 3 Factos, Black Defendant/White Victim, 2006 May 20 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Data Reports - n=16, Death 1, 3 Factos, White Victims, 2006 May 20 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Data Reports - n=16, Death 1, White Victim, 2 Scales, 2006 May 20 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Data Reports - Sentence Before CA Review Screen, 2006 May 20 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Factors and Scales - Data Reports, Handwritten Notes, 2006 May 20; 2006 May 24 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Raw Data - DCI List, all in put variables, in binder, 2006 May 20; 2006 May 31 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - SAS Recode for Year of Offense, 2006 May 20 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - Screening and Scale Page, 2006 May 22; 2006 June 1 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Logit Screen and Salient Factors, 2006 May 22-25 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Reading Notes - For May Screen, Data Report, 2006 May 22; 2006 June 2; 2006 June 10 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Screening Overview, 2006 May 22 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Data Reports - High Aggravating Factors, 2006 May 24 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Purges - Woodworth G, 2006 May 24 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - George Woodworth - Stat Tests, 2006 May 24 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Development of Military Law and Death Penalty - Historical Overview, Documents 1-11, Footnotes 1, 4-19, 21-24, 27, 33-35, 20-41, 2006 May 25 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Development of Military Law and Death Penalty - Historical Overview, Documents 12-15, Footnoes 28-31, 33-29, 50, 2006 May 25 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Development of Military Law and Death Penalty - Historical Overview, Documents 16-25, Footnotes 42-49, 51-57, 59, 2006 May 25 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Shades of Black - "Black' features can sway in favor of death penalty, according to study,", 2006 May 25 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - New Variables, 2006 May 26; 2006 May 30 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Race Results Data Reports - Capital Sentencing Hearing Death Sentence Regression, 2006 May 31-June 1 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Race Results Data Reports - Capital Sentencing Hearing Regressions, 2006 May 31; 2006 June 2 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Race Results Data Reports - Staff Judge Advocate (SJA) Regression and Crosstab, 2006 May 31 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Define Standard MACROS, 2006 May (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - JEHT Foundation Grant - Supplemental Request, ca. 2006 May (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - J. Robert Lilly, "Dirty Details: Executing U.S. Soldiers During World War 2, ca. 2006 May (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Military Briefs - Moureen buller points, ca. 2006 May (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Military Briefs - United States V. Curtis, ca. 2006 May (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Military Briefs - United States V. Gray, ca. 2006 May (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Military Briefs - United States V. Loving, ca. 2006 May (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Dwight H. Sullivan, "Two Decades of Military Capiatal Litigation, ", ca. 2006 May (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Race Cleaning, 2006 June 1 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Race Results Data Reports - CA Seek, Race Death Scale, 2006 June 1 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Race Results Data Reports - Capital Sentencing Hewig Death Scale, 2006 June 1 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Race Results Data Reports - Capital Sentencing Hearing Death Sentence, Death Scale, 2006 June 1 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Race Results Data Reports - Death 1 Scale, Race Effects, 2006 June 1 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Capital Sentencing Hearing Regression, June 30 Draft, 2006 June 2 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Data Reports - Capital Sentencing Hearing - Death Sentence, Race, 2006 June 2 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Data Reports - Capital Sentencing Hearing, Race, 2006 June 2 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Data Reports - Two Victim, CA Seek - Race, 2006 June 2 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Figure 19 Drafts, 2006 June 2; 2006 July 23; 2006 October 16 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Old Tables and Figures - Figure 17, Data Reports, Handwritten Notes, 2006 June 2 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - One Victim Models - Unadjusted Regressions, 2006 June 2 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Correspondence - Tables and Figures List, 2006 June 5 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - History of Military Death Penalty, Cox Commission, World War 2, 2006 June 6; Undated (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Missing Race, 2006 June 6 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - CA Seek Models, 2006 June 7 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Capital Sentencing Hearing Regression - Race, 2006 June 7 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Data Reports - Capital Sentencing Hearing Death Sentence (CSH DTH) Scales, All Cap [?], 2006 June 7 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - One Victim Models - Advance to Trial with Government Seeking Death Penalty, 2006 June 7 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - One Victim Models - Capital Sentencing Hearing Held, 2006 June 7 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - One Victim Models - Death Sentence before CA Review, 2006 June 7 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Exact Tests - Correspondence with George Woodworth, 2006 June 9 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Data Reports - Non Unanimous Crosstab by Accused, 2006 June 9 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Military Case Summaries, 2006 June 10 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Data Reports - Changes on Time, 2006 June 11-12 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Data Reports - Year of Scales, 2006 June 11 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Background Research - Documents A1 - A7, 2006 June 12; 2006 June 18; 2006 July 6; 2006 July 20 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Background Research - Documents A8 - A16, 2006 June 12; 2006 June 18; 2006 July 6; 2006 July 20 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Background Research - Documents A17 - A31, 2006 June 12; 2006 June 18; 2006 July 6; 2006 July 20 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Combined Fixes, Recordes, Purge and Scale, 2006 June 12 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Data Reports - Mits and Aggryntes [?], 2006 June 12 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Data Reports - New Scale DTH, 2006 June 12 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - NUM AGG [Number of Aggrivating factors?], 2006 June 12-14 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Consistancy Analysis - Proportionality Review, 2006 June 14 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Data Reports - Amalgamation Model, 2006 June 14 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Data Reports - Non Unanimous, 2006 June 14 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Data Reports - Race Regressions, 2006 June 14 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Data Reports - Before and After 1990, 2006 June 15 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Data Reports - Number of Aggravating Circumstances, Crosstabs, 2006 June 15-16 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Data Reports - Year of Sentence, 2006 June 15 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Data Reports - 16 Cases, Two Victim Cases, 2006 June 16 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Salient Factor Scale, White Victim, 2006 June 16 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Data Reports - Scales: Enhanced Mantel Haentzel, Factos - SCL, Race Scales, 2006 June 16 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Figure 20 Drafts, 2006 June 16; 2006 July 21 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence - Origins of Military Death Penalty Study and Wilmer Hale Involvement, 2006 June 19 (Box 8, Folder 28)